Guide to the Yoshio Kishi and Irene Yah-Ling Sun Collection 1860-2010 MSS.292
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Yoshio Kishi's Files
  - Subseries F: Subject Files
    - Gee, Yun; Ikeda, Li-Lan, Undated (Box 35, Folder 45)
    - Genealogy, Asian, 1972-1973, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 46)
    - Gilbert, Rodney, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 47)
    - Glazier, Captain W., 1886 (Box 35, Folder 48)
    - Glossary, Undated (Box 35, Folder 49)
    - Gobineau, Comte de, 1878 (Box 35, Folder 50)
    - Godzilla, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 51)
    - The Good Earth, Undated (Box 35, Folder 52)
    - Grant, Maxwell - "The Shadow", 1975 (Box 35, Folder 53)
    - Griffis, William Elliot, 1888 (Box 35, Folder 54)
    - Gueulette, M. - "Chinese Tales", 1781 (Box 35, Folder 55)
    - Hamanaka, Lionelle, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 56)
    - Hanson, Carter F., 1995 (Box 35, Folder 57)
    - Harada, T. - "The Japanese Problem in California", 1920 (Box 35, Folder 58)
    - Hardesty, Undated (Box 35, Folder 59)
    - Harper's Magazine, 1942 (Box 35, Folder 60)
    - Harte, Bret, 1979, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 61)
    - Hartmann, Sadakichi, Undated (Box 35, Folder 62)
    - Hawaii, 1972-1974, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 63)
    - Hayakawa, S.I., 1972, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 64)
    - Hayakawa, Sessue, 1997, 1999, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 65)
    - Hearn, Lefcadio, 1988-2002 (Box 35, Folder 66)
    - Hearst, William Randolph, Undated (Box 35, Folder 67)
    - Heathen Chinee, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 68)
    - Hiebert, A., 1971 (Box 35, Folder 69)
    - Hiroshima-Nagasaki, 1970, 1975, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 70)
    - Historiography, Undated (Box 35, Folder 71)
    - "Hito Hata", 1980-1981 (Box 35, Folder 72)
    - Ho, Fred Wei-Han, 1985-1989 (Box 35, Folder 73)
    - Holley, Marietta, 1881 (Box 35, Folder 74)
    - Homelessness, Undated (Box 35, Folder 75)
    - Hoover, J. Edgar, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 76)
    - Howe, James Wong, 1973, 1974, 1978, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 77)
    - Howey, M. Oldfield - "The Encircled Serpent", Undated (Box 35, Folder 78)
    - Hoyt, Charles H., 1940 (Box 35, Folder 79)
    - Hsieh, Ren, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 80)
    - Hurwitz, Leo, 2007, 2010 (Box 35, Folder 81)
    - Hwang, David Henry, 1988, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 82)
    - Hyun, Peter, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 83)
    - I.L.G.W.U. - "Made in Japan" campaign, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 84)
    - Immigration, Undated (Box 35, Folder 85)
    - Immigration, East Indian, 1977, Undated (Box 35, Folder 86)
    - Inada, Hide Ikehara, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 87)
    - Inouye, Daniel K., 1973, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 88)
    - Internet and Evacuation, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 89)
    - Invisible Citizens - Japanese Americans, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 90)
    - Iraq and Japan, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 91)
    - Irwin, Will, Undated (Box 35, Folder 92)
    - Ishiguro, Kazuo, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 93)
    - Ishii, David, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 94)
    - Ito, Michio, 1923-1936 (Box 35, Folder 95)
    - Ivano, Paul, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 96)
    - Jackson, Donald Dale, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 97)
    - Janacel, Leos, 1990, 1993, 2007 (Box 35, Folder 98)
    - "Jap", 1971 (Box 35, Folder 99)
    - Japan, Undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Japan, Acquisitions by, 1988-1990 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Japan and the West, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Japan, Auto Industry, 1980-1991 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Japan Bashing, 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Japan Bibliography, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Japan, Books on, 1906, 1988, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Japan, Early contact with, Undated (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Japan in Fiction, 1984, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Japan - films, Undated (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Japan, First mission to the U.S., 1860 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Japan Foundation, 1979-2001 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Japan - G.I. Babies, Undated (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Japan, Images of, Undated (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - "Japan Inc.", 1987-1990 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Japan, Koreans in, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Japan, U.S. views of, Undated (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Japanese American Citizens League, 1971-1974 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Japanese American Curriculum Project, 1991-1994 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Japanese American Exhibits, 1987-1988, Undated (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Japanese Americans, Films on, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Japanese Americans for Confrotation and Liberation, Undated (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Japanese American Library, San Francisco, 1986-1990 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Japanese American National Museum, 1988-1998 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - "Japanese in Americas", T. Furuhata K.B.K.K., Undated (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Japanese American Social Services, Inc., 1988 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Japanese Associations, Undated (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Japanese in the U.S. - clippings, Undated (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Japanese and Jews, 1972, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Japanese Pacific Resource Network, 1987-1991 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Japanese Photography, Undated (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Japanese Restaurants, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Japanese Studies in the U.S., 1988 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Japanese Theater in the U.S., Undated (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Japonisme, 1975, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Japanophile, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Jazz, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - "Jewish" articles, 2008-2009 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Johnson, Harry M. - "Edith, A Story of Chinatown", 1895 (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - Johnson, Samuel, 1945 (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - Journalists, Asian American, 1988, Undated (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Jue, Joseph Sunn, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - Jung, C.G., 2009 (Box 36, Folder 43)
    - Kalayaan, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 44)
    - Kang, Dr. Thomas H. - Core Committee on Asian American Materials, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 45)
    - Kanjincho, Undated (Box 36, Folder 46)
    - Kanzaki, K. - "California and the Japanese", 1921 (Box 36, Folder 47)
    - Kasai Collection, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 48)
    - Kawakami, Kiyoshi Karl, 1912, 1932 (Box 36, Folder 49)
    - Keeler, Harry Steven, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 50)
    - Kenzo of J.A.P., 1972 (Box 36, Folder 51)
    - Kepley, Vance, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 52)
    - Kim, Elaine H. - "Room for a View...", 2003 (Box 36, Folder 53)
    - Kitagawa, D. - "Issei and Nisei", 1974 (Box 36, Folder 54)
    - Knee, Allan - Santa Anita '42, Undated (Box 36, Folder 55)
    - Kobre, Sidney, Undated (Box 36, Folder 56)
    - Kochiyama, William and Mary, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 57)
    - Kogawa, Joy, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Konishi - "Bridge" television series proposal, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Korea - photos, Undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Korea, 1971-1972, 1988, Undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - The Korea Society, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Koreans in the United States, 1975-1976, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Krutnik, Frank, Undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Kudaka, Geraldine - "Persona" booklet of poetry, Undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Kung Fu, 1971-1975 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Kuo, Nina, Undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Kushner, Eve - "Dis-Orientation: Japan", 2003 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Kuwa, George, Undated (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Kyne, Peter B., 1974 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - "The Last Emperor", 1987 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Latin America, Asians in, 1876, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - LEAP Asian American Public Policy Institute, 1995-1996 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Lee, Lee C. and Feng, Kathay, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Lee, Spike, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Leland, Charles Godfrey, 1906 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Leong, Russell (1 of 2), 1982-1992 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Leong, Russell (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Leyda, Jay, 1956-1988 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Libraries - private, 2001-2008 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Library of Congress, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Ling, Amy, 2000, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - The Literary Digest, Undated (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - "A Little Family Business", 1982 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - "Little Tokyo" - Translation of NHK film (narration only), Undated (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - London, Jack, Undated (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Long, John Luther, 1904 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Los Angeles Asian Pacific American International Film Festival, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - Loti, Pierre, 1890, Undated (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Lotus, Hunter College, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Lovecraft, H.P., Undated (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Lum, Wing Tek, 1970, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - "M. Butterfly", 1988 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - "Madame Butterfly", 1907, 1989-1995, Undated (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - Mandelbaum, Allen, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - Manga, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - Mannequins, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - Manson, Marsden - "The Yellow Peril in Action" master, 1907 (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - Markino, Yoshio, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - Marquand, J.P., Undated (Box 37, Folder 43)
    - Martial Arts, 1904 (Box 37, Folder 44)
    - Mascagni, Pietro - "Iris", 1898 (Box 37, Folder 45)
    - Matsuda, Thomas, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 46)
    - McNeill, George E. - "The Labor Movement", 1971 (Box 37, Folder 47)
    - McWilliams, Carey, Undated (Box 37, Folder 48)
    - Mei, Lan-Fang, 1930, 1959, Undated (Box 37, Folder 49)
    - Meiji-Mura, 1990, Undated (Box 37, Folder 50)
    - Mid-Atlantic Conference on Community Concerns..., 1974 (Box 37, Folder 51)
    - "Midnight in Chinatown", 2004 (Box 37, Folder 52)
    - The Mikado, 1985-1988 (Box 37, Folder 53)
    - The Mikado - Kushner, Eve, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 54)
    - Millard, Thomas F., Undated (Box 37, Folder 55)
    - Minorities in Media, 1972-1990 (Box 37, Folder 56)
    - "Miss Saigon", 1990, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 57)
    - Mixed Marriages, 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 58)
    - Miyao, Daisuke, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 59)
    - Mongolism, Undated (Box 37, Folder 60)
    - Monkeys, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 61)
    - Moore, Colleen, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 62)
    - Morris, Narrelle, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 63)
    - Movie Posters, Lobby Cards, Stills, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 64)
    - Moving the Image - book, 1990-1992 (Box 37, Folder 65)
    - Mr. Wong, Detective, 1938-1939 (Box 37, Folder 66)
    - Mr. Wu, 1914 (Box 37, Folder 67)
    - Mukherjee, Bharati, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 68)
    - Munch, Edvard, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 69)
    - Mura, David, 1988-1989, 1991, Undated (Box 37, Folder 70)
    - The Museum of Modern Art, Undated (Box 37, Folder 71)
    - Music, 1972, 1998, 2006, 2008, Undated (Box 37, Folder 72)
    - Music, Asia in, Undated (Box 37, Folder 73)
    - Music, Asian, 1973-1990 (Box 37, Folder 74)
    - Music, Asians in, 1926, 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 75)
    - Music, Chinatown in, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 76)
    - Music, Japan in, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 77)
    - Musicians, Asian (images), Undated (Box 37, Folder 78)
    - Musicians, Asian American, 1976, 1980, Undated (Box 37, Folder 79)
    - Myths and Perceptions, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 80)
    - Naipaul, V.S., 1975-1989 (Box 37, Folder 81)
    - Narita, Cobi, 2001, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 82)
    - Nast, Thomas, Undated (Box 37, Folder 83)
    - National Asian American Telecommunications Network, 1989-1991, Undated (Box 37, Folder 84)
    - National Asian Pacific Center on Aging, 1992-1993 (Box 37, Folder 85)
    - National Association og Asian American Professionals, 1987-1990 (Box 37, Folder 86)
    - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations, Inc., 1972 (Box 37, Folder 87)
    - National Council for Japanese American Redress, Chicago, 1987-1989 (Box 37, Folder 88)
    - National Japanese American Historical Society, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 89)
    - National Portrait Gallery - "Politics of Portraiture", 1990 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Negru, Mathew M., 1974-1987 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Netrebko, Anna, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - The New Asian Standard, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - New Republic, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - New York Asian Women's Center, 1991-1992 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - New York Chinatown History Project, 1982-1991 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - New York State Archives, Albany, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Nikkei Review, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Nikkei Sentinal, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Ninja, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Noguchi, Hideo, Undated (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Noguchi, Isamu, Undated (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Noguchi, Yone, 1943 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - The Oi School Japan-American Sumi-E Club, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Okada, John - "No-No Boy", 1976 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Okinawa, Undated (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Okubo, Mine, 2000-2001 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Ono, Yoko, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Opium, Undated (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Organization of Chinese Americans, 1986-1992 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Oriental Actors of America, Undated (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Overseas Asians, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Overseas Chinese, 1971-1972, 1981, Undated (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Ozaki, Milton K., 1999 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Pacific Overtures, 1975-1976 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Pan Asian Repertory Theatre, NYC, Undated (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Paper Angels, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Pei, I.M., 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Peking Man, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Penny Dreadfuls and Thrillers, 1974, Undated (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - People, Personalities, Etc..., 1929, 1974-1976, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Phillips, Gene D., 1973 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - PHP Intersect, 1985-1990 (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - Pinyin, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Porter, Gene Stratton, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - Postcards, 1975-1981 (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - Powers, Kare and Family, 2009 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Prejudice, 1987-1990, Undated (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - The Pride and Shame Exhibit - Seattle JACL, 1972, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - Prostitution, Asian Americans, 1898, 1977, 1987, Undated (Box 38, Folder 41)
    - Public Opinion, Undated (Box 38, Folder 42)
    - "The Purcell Recorder", Undated (Box 38, Folder 43)
    - Put's Original California Songster, 1868 (Box 38, Folder 44)
    - Putnam's Magazine, 1869 (Box 38, Folder 45)
    - Racism, Undated (Box 38, Folder 46)
    - Racism of Japanese, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 47)
    - Rare Oriental Book Company, 1993-1996 (Box 38, Folder 48)
    - Redress, 1981-1990 (Box 38, Folder 49)
    - Religions of Asia, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 50)
    - Rice (magazine), 1988 (Box 38, Folder 51)
    - "Ride the Winds", 1974 (Box 38, Folder 52)
    - Riis, Jacob, 1904 (Box 38, Folder 53)
    - Robots, 2002-2006 (Box 38, Folder 54)
    - Rogin, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 55)
    - Rohmer, Sax - Fu Manchu, Undated (Box 38, Folder 56)
    - Ross, Clifford, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 57)
    - Rukeyser, Muriel, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 58)
    - Rushdie, Salman, 1988-1990 (Box 38, Folder 59)
    - Russo-Japanese War, 1911 (Box 38, Folder 60)
    - Schomburg Center for Research in Black Culture, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 61)
    - Scribner's Monthly, 1871 (Box 38, Folder 62)
    - Seattle Cherry Blossom, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 63)
    - See, Lisa, 2003, 2010 (Box 38, Folder 64)
    - Shanghai Mercury - The Boxer Rising 1900, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 65)
    - Sherman, Undated (Box 38, Folder 66)
    - Shimoda, Yuki, Undated (Box 38, Folder 67)
    - Shimono et al Vs. The Repertory Theater of Lincoln Center, Inc. et al, 1973, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 68)
    - Silent Movie Stars, Undated (Box 38, Folder 69)
    - Siu, Paul C.P., Undated (Box 38, Folder 70)
    - Sojin, 2000, Undated (Box 38, Folder 71)
    - Sone, Monica - "Nisei Daughter, 1953 (Box 38, Folder 72)
    - Soon, Terence Tam, Undated (Box 38, Folder 73)
    - Southeast Asians, 1980, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 74)
    - Sowell, Thomas - "Ethnic America", 1981 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Spencer, Herbert, 1820-1903, 1904 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - "Station J", 1982 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Steichen, Joanna, 1982, 2010 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Stereotypes, 1972-2002 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Sternberg, Josef von, 1966, Undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Stewart, Harry, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Stone Facades, 2009 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Stone, Grace Zaring, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Stoppard, Tom, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Student Publications, 1988, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Students, Asian American, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Sugimoto, Henry, 1978, 1984, 1990, Undated (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Tachiki, Dennis, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Taiwanese American Citizens League, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Takagi, Tokuko Nagai, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Takemitsu, Toru, Undated (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Tam Brothers, Boston, 1975-1976 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Tan, Amy, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Tanforan Totalizer, 1942-1943 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Tank, Kee - "China and the Chinese", Undated (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Taylor, Benj. F. - "Between the Gates", 1878 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - "Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles", 1990 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Television, Images of Asians, 1988, Undated (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Textbooks, Asian Americans in, 1947, 1971, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Textbooks, Japan in, 1988, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Thai, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Theater, Asian American, 1974, 1987-1989 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Theater, Japanese, 1930-1931, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - The Third World Bicentennial Forum, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Third World Media News, Undated (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Ting, Wallasse, 1966, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Tokyo Rose, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Townsend, Edward W., Undated (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Triad, 1873 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - The Tsing Hua Journal 2:1, 1916 (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - Tuchman, B.W., 1981 (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - Tundra Books, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - Tuska, Jon - "The Detective in Hollywood", 1978 (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - Twain, Mark - "Early Tales and Sketches", 1979 (Box 39, Folder 40)
    - Tyre, Peg, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 41)
    - Uchida, N. - "The Overseas Chinese", 1959 (Box 39, Folder 42)
    - Uchida, Yoshiko, Undated (Box 39, Folder 43)
    - Union of Activists, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 44)
    - United States Committee for Refugees, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 45)
    - United States Commission on Civil Rights, 1992, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 46)
    - United States Congress - Subversive Activities Control Act of 1950 (Box 39, Folder 47)
    - United States Department of State, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 48)
    - United States, Japanese views of, 1972, 1988, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 49)
    - University of California, L.A. - Asian American Studies Center, 1981-2002 (Box 39, Folder 50)
    - Uno, Edison, 1965, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 51)
    - "Unreserved Auction of Black Americana", 1989 (Box 39, Folder 52)
    - Vietnam, 1972-1990 (Box 39, Folder 53)
    - Vietnam, Films on, 1979-1989 (Box 39, Folder 54)
    - Vietnam War Literature, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 55)
    - Vietnamese in the U.S., 1973-1991 (Box 39, Folder 56)
    - Vinyl Records, 2009, 2011, Undated (Box 39, Folder 57)
    - Visual Communications / AASC, Inc., Undated (Box 39, Folder 58)
    - von Sternberg, Meri, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 59)
    - Walcott, Derek, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 60)
    - Wang, Charles B., 2003 (Box 39, Folder 61)
    - War Statistics, 1971, Undated (Box 39, Folder 62)
    - Weinberg, Herman G., Undated (Box 39, Folder 63)
    - Whitney, Atwell - "Almond Eyed", 1878 (Box 39, Folder 64)
    - "The Widows' House", Undated (Box 39, Folder 65)
    - Wolfe, Tom - "The Yellow Peril", 1970 (Box 39, Folder 66)
    - Woltor, R. - "Short and Truthful", 1882 (Box 39, Folder 67)
    - The Woman Warrior", 1979 (Box 39, Folder 68)
    - Wong, Anna May, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 69)
    - World War I, 1918 (Box 39, Folder 70)
    - Writers, Asian American, 1976, 1987, 1989, Undated (Box 39, Folder 71)
    - Wyoming, Governer - Chinese Labor Troubles, 1885 (Box 39, Folder 72)
    - Yee, Albert H., Undated (Box 39, Folder 73)
    - "Yellow-Face", Undated (Box 39, Folder 74)
    - "Yellow is my Favorite Color", 1981 (Box 39, Folder 75)
    - Yellow Journalism, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 76)
    - "Yellow Peril", 1904-1922, 1990-2006 (Box 39, Folder 77)
    - Yep, Laurence, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 78)
    - Yokeda, Karl G., Undated (Box 39, Folder 79)
    - Yoshimura, Wendy, 1975-1976 (Box 39, Folder 80)
    - "Yoshio Kishi" Google search results, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 81)
    - Young / Chin Legal Aid Committee, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 82)
    - Boddy, Manchester - from California Historical Society Quarterly [Flat Box], Undated (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Subseries G: Scrutable Image
    - Slides of Images of Asians / Asian Americans, Undated (Binder A)
  - Subseries H: Filmmaking
    - "An Appointment with Sessue and Anna May" screenplay by Kishi and Sun, Undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Budget form - typed draft, 1982, Undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - "The Celluloid Society" proposal master, Undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Editing - equipment rental, Undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - "Empress of China" proposal, Undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - "Empress of China" proposal (Videotrope Cinema projects), Undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - "Empress of China" proposal (Videotrope Cinema projects), 1978 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Erich von Stroheim - reference material, 1977-1978 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - "The Fatal Goddess" budget (Videotrope Cinema projects), Undated (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - "The Fatal Goddess" general, Undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - "The Fatal Goddess" proposal master, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - "The Fatal Goddess" screenplay, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - The Film Fund, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - The Film Fund - grant application, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Film making file, 1945, 1957-1964, Undated (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Film manuals (1 of 2), 1953-1967 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Film Manuals (2 of 2), 1954-1966 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - "The Great Collaboration: Achievement in Cinema" proposal, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - "The Great Collaboration" budget, Undated (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - "The Great Collaboration" proposal master, Undated (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - "The Hollywood Connection..." proposal, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Independent Documentary Fund Application, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - "Johnny Zee" screenplay, Undated (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - "Johnny Zee" screenplay, Undated (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - "Khan: Death Imports Incorporated" by Kishi and Kirschheimer, Undated (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Movies about Movies - service supplement, Undated (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - [Nil] Projects, 1977, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Production Forms - budget, Undated (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Proposals and funding applications, Undated (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Releases, Undated (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Reports and papers on mass communications..., 1956 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Tape - Magnetic - info, Undated (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - WGBH - Boston, David Lacey, 1978-1979 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - WNET - Channel 13 screening, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 34)
- Series VII: Audio
  This series contains audio recordings, mostly of movies, as well as paper materials with information and notes about the recordings.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Audio materials have not been preserved and are not be available to researchers.
  - Subseries A: Access Copies
  - Subseries B: Originals
    - The American Assassins part I, 11/25/1975 (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0001)
      General
      Format: Audiocassette
    - "Asian Americans for Action" - AAA [Hting] - Furutani, etc. Fri 7/7/72, 1972 (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0002)
    - "Asian Ameican Reality conf." Sunday 12/6/70 - Roll 1 side A, Roll 1 side B, 1970 (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0003)
    - "Asian American Reality conf." Sunday 12/6/70 - Roll 2 side A, 1970 (Box 78, Cassette ID: 292.0004)